<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team Last Responders</title>
    <description>Team Last Responders adventures for charity</description>
    <link>http://lastresponders.org/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://lastresponders.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 11:56:05 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 11:56:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Team Last Responders</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team Last Responders&lt;/strong&gt; is a community of like-minded volunteers who believe that travel is not only a mechanism to connect with people around the world, but also a way to experience and to understand charitable work at the ground level. Team members embark on adventures and narrate the personal story of their journey to an audience largely built through social media. By placing the charity at the conclusion of the story, Last Responders aims to relate a real philanthropic work to a real-life personal story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2010 as Team MMT (short for the initial team name Team Magical Mongolian Mystery Tour), Team MMT inc is a registered 501(c)3 non-profit that exists to promote partner charities and raise funds to assist their efforts. The primary means we add value to our charity partners:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raise visibility&lt;/strong&gt; of our charity partners by including them in our story&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Raise funding&lt;/strong&gt; (direct and indirect) for our charity partners either directly&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Material donations&lt;/strong&gt; to support activities on the ground&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To date, our organization has participated in three charity rallies. In 2010, as Team Magical Mongolian Mystery Tour, the team drove 10,000 miles from London to Ulan Bator, Mongolia and chose &lt;a href=&quot;www.msf.org&quot;&gt;Doctors Without Borders&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mercycorp.org&quot;&gt;Mercycorp&lt;/a&gt; as our benefactors. In 2011, as Team Last Responders, the team drove 4,000 miles from London to Bamako, Mali choosing the &lt;a href=&quot;http://malihealth.org&quot;&gt;Mali Health Organizing Project&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.salifkeita.us&quot;&gt;Salif Keita Global Foundation&lt;/a&gt; to be our partners. In 2014, the PanAmerican Rally took the team from New York to Tujillo, Peru and the team partnered with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.esperanca.org&quot;&gt;Esperanca&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.viveperu.org&quot;&gt;Vive Peru&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;team@lastresponders.org&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Address&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2373 Broadway #828&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;New York, NY 10024&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2016/01/23/AboutUs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2016/01/23/AboutUs.html</guid>
        
        <category>modal-aboutus</category>
        
        
        <category>modal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pan American Rally 2014</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Pan American Rally was a Team Last Responders ‘first’. For this project, the team designed a route, planned a time table and organized the vehicle donation without the assistance of an organizer. Over the course of the project, the team raised money, donated medical supplies, and delivered two vehicles to our partner charities - Vive Peru and Esperanca.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2014/07/20/PanAmericanRally2014.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2014/07/20/PanAmericanRally2014.html</guid>
        
        <category>modal-rally</category>
        
        
        <category>modal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Timbuktu Challenge 2012</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Timbuktu Challenge is a 4,000 miles car rally that starts in London and ends near Timbuktu, Mali. For this event, teams acquire cars for donation, gather in London and drive to Western Africa in 3 weeks. Team Last Responders answered the call to adventure with an Made-in-USA Wheeled Coach Ambulance and went the extra mile of shipping the car to Liverpool from New York.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2014/07/19/TimbuktuChallenge2012.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2014/07/19/TimbuktuChallenge2012.html</guid>
        
        <category>modal-rally</category>
        
        
        <category>modal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mongol Rally 2010</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Mongol Rally is the ultimate endurance rally that covers the insane distance of 10,000 miles from London UK to Ulan Bator, Mongolia. In the summer of 2010, Team Last Responders joined teams from around the world to attempt this challenge. For this first  charity rally, the team raised money and donated an ambulance benefiting MSF, Mercycorp, and the country of Mongolia.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2014/07/18/MongolRally2010.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2014/07/18/MongolRally2010.html</guid>
        
        <category>modal-rally</category>
        
        
        <category>modal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Everything is Perfect at Home</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;1.&amp;nbsp; We were all rushed onto the plane in Lima, and I had to use the bathroom before the plane took off.&amp;nbsp; I was so very happy that the toilet paper can be flushed down the toilet.&lt;&amp;#47;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.&amp;nbsp; By the time we landed in Florida, everybody spoke English,&amp;nbsp; I understood every word of every conversation, all the signs were familiar too.&lt;&amp;#47;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.&amp;nbsp; It took about 3 minutes to re-connect my cellphone.&amp;nbsp; I got my unlimited LTE network back while waiting for my connecting flight.&lt;&amp;#47;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.&amp;nbsp; When I finally arrived in Baltimore and met my mom at the baggage claim, my first word was, &amp;ldquo;mama.&amp;rdquo;&amp;nbsp; My mom said, &amp;ldquo;Oh, you didn&amp;rsquo;t lose any weight.&amp;rdquo;&lt;&amp;#47;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.&amp;nbsp; I slept on my full size bed with soft clean sheets I chose and purchased to my liking.&amp;nbsp; I have my own bed, my own bedroom, my own bathroom, my own study, no need to share anymore.&lt;&amp;#47;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.&amp;nbsp; I showered as long as I wanted, applied conditioner on my hair and even had a facial mask.&amp;nbsp; The next day, I showered twice, in fact, I can shower as many times as I want.&lt;&amp;#47;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7.&amp;nbsp; I have plenty of clean clothes.&lt;&amp;#47;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8.&amp;nbsp; 回家后第一顿饭吃的是凉瓜，皮蛋拌豆腐等清爽的小菜。吃饭的时候，面上无事，心里很感慨呀。然后第二天买了一条活鱼回来，总算吃到了真正的新鲜鱼。&lt;&amp;#47;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9.&amp;nbsp; We&amp;rsquo;ll get to see all of you who supported us.&amp;nbsp; Thank you for everything.&lt;&amp;#47;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2014 16:44:16 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2014/05/17/everything-is-perfect-at-home.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2014/05/17/everything-is-perfect-at-home.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Cathy</category>
        
        <category>South America Rally 2013</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Esperanca</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Clean water. Safe housing. Nutritious food. Esperança envisions a world in which the foundations of health and well being are available to people everywhere. For more than four decades it has joined with communities worldwide, providing tools, training, and support necessary to help them reach that goal. Team Last Responders partnered with Esperança in 2013 for the PanAmerican Rally. On the journey, the team visited their offices in Phoenix, Nicaragua, and Bolivia, learning about the many challenges that these developing communities face.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2014/05/01/Esperanca.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2014/05/01/Esperanca.html</guid>
        
        <category>partners</category>
        
        
        <category>modal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vive Peru</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Vive Perú is a nonprofit organization dedicated to fostering understanding of Peruvian culture and providing aid to Peruvian communities. For the PanAmerican Rally, Vive Peru bravely accepted the responsibility to receive and integrate the Last Responders ambulance into the Trujillo medical network. Reaching Trujillo, the team discovered an organization committed to making an impact in struggling neighborhoods, orphanages, and hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2014/05/01/VivePeru.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2014/05/01/VivePeru.html</guid>
        
        <category>partners</category>
        
        
        <category>modal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Far is My Dream?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;lastresponders.org&amp;#47;wp-content&amp;#47;uploads&amp;#47;2014&amp;#47;04&amp;#47;stars.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;padding-top: 0px;padding-left: 0px;padding-right: 0px;border-width: 0px&quot; title=&quot;stars&quot; alt=&quot;stars&quot; src=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;lastresponders.org&amp;#47;wp-content&amp;#47;uploads&amp;#47;2014&amp;#47;04&amp;#47;stars_thumb.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1028&quot; height=&quot;685&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; &amp;#47;&gt;&lt;&amp;#47;a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took this picture on the high mountains roughly 30 miles north of Camargo, Bolivia.&amp;nbsp; I&amp;rsquo;m not sure whether I had the Milky Way or a nebula,&amp;nbsp; all I knew was that I won&amp;rsquo;t be able to see this at home because stars of the southern hemisphere are different from the northern hemisphere.&amp;nbsp; At the time, we were driving thousands of meters above the sea level on dangerous curvy mountain roads, there were a couple of street lamps distanced away, cars passed by very rarely on the road.&amp;nbsp; I requested to stop for pictures, the moment I opened the passenger door of the ambulance, I saw the night sky I&amp;rsquo;ve dreamed of for years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by heavenly bodies. My first attempt to photograph the moon was about ten years ago, using my first digital camera, the pocket sized Casio Exilim.&amp;nbsp; The Casio Exilim had some manual settings which allowed me to do long exposures on a tripod for night scenes, but unfortunately, the moon didn&amp;rsquo;t come out well.&amp;nbsp; Since then, I failed a few more times to capture the moon and the stars as I had hoped.&amp;nbsp; The moon was my trials of failures before success, just before this trip, I borrowed my dad&amp;rsquo;s Nikon D700 and took a couple of satisfying pictures of the moon.&amp;nbsp; The Milky Way, on the other hand, has been a fantasy that I only saw in textbooks and online tutorials.&amp;nbsp; I&amp;rsquo;ve never even seen the Milky Way with my own eyes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The moment I stepped out of the car, I knew that a dream was coming true, I walked into the phantom night sky shown on textbooks and NASA pictures.&amp;nbsp; Immediately, I fetched the camera and the tripod, it was my chance to produce a textbook picture!&amp;nbsp; When I took this picture, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t see anything through the view finder because it was too dark.&amp;nbsp; I aimed at a section of the sky and pressed the shutter, 30 seconds later, I discovered what the picture looked like, then adjusted the camera settings and the angle of the camera to try again.&amp;nbsp; While I gazed at the millions of stars, waiting for the exposure to finish, I wished for a wider lens which could get more coverage, I wished for our more experienced photographer Mike to be here, maybe Mike would have a clever way to position the camera to get the village at the far horizon.&amp;nbsp; There were no shooting stars to grant my wishes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few shots I realized my lens was only able to capture a small fraction of the grandiose sky, nonetheless, a small fraction was enough to produce my splendid picture.&amp;nbsp; A more experienced photographer with better equipment would definitely be able to compose a more gorgeous shot, but when nature is so magnificent, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take much talent to produce a great picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps my picture only demonstrates 20% of nature&amp;rsquo;s greatness, maybe a more professional photographer would be twice as good, but no pictures or words can do nature justice.&amp;nbsp; You must stand high above the sea level, breath in diluted oxygen, and feel the cold breeze in the quiet darkness to live our stargazing experience.&amp;nbsp; It is not humanly possible to replicate this fantastic moment.&amp;nbsp; We can share our pictures and videos, tell our stories, but we cannot bring anyone to live the experience, you must adventure out there yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We resigned from our jobs, drove ten thousand miles and traveled four months on the road, then of all a sudden, one night, I stepped out of the vehicle and realized my long cherished dream.&amp;nbsp; Sounds very amazing, right?&amp;nbsp; I stared at this picture for a while in solitude (please understand that to be in solitude is very had for me, I&amp;rsquo;m now used to eating, sleeping, and doing almost everything accompanied by someone else) and questioned myself what it really takes for me to produce something like this.&amp;nbsp; First, I need a camera with long exposure capability, that&amp;rsquo;s not hard, I have many friends with good cameras and lenses.&amp;nbsp; Then, I need to go to a place to take this picture.&amp;nbsp; For at least 3 years, I knew Cherry Springs State Park in Pennsylvania is famous for stargazing, and this state park is about 4 or 5 hours away from Manhattan.&amp;nbsp; Well, so what does it take to borrow a camera, rent a car, and drive there to take pictures?&amp;nbsp; It&amp;rsquo;s one day&amp;rsquo;s work?&amp;nbsp; Make two days?&amp;nbsp; Why didn&amp;rsquo;t I go?&amp;nbsp; On a chilly clear night, way up high in the Bolivian mountains, I realized that perhaps some dreams were never too far away, I just didn&amp;rsquo;t chase them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 03:45:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2014/04/27/how-far-is-my-dream.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2014/04/27/how-far-is-my-dream.html</guid>
        
        <category>Last Responders</category>
        
        <category>South America Rally 2014</category>
        
        <category>Pan American Rally</category>
        
        <category>lastresponders</category>
        
        <category>milky way</category>
        
        <category>stargazing</category>
        
        <category>stars</category>
        
        
        <category>Cathy</category>
        
        <category>South America Rally 2013</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>In Boredom</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On our way to La Paz, Bolivia, my typical day starts with waking up in the ambulance in a gas station, getting out of the sleeping bag, brushing my teeth, make some oatmeal if an electrical outlet was available for our water boiler, decide on plans for the day with everybody, and then we begin to drive.&amp;nbsp; The driver always has a navigator in the front, so one person would be left in body of the ambulance.&amp;nbsp; If I&amp;rsquo;m not the one driving, I usually become bored easily.&amp;nbsp; Data connectivity becomes rare on our smartphones while we drive through the deserts&amp;#47;mountains.&amp;nbsp; We have a couple of novels, but it&amp;rsquo;s difficult to read while the vehicle is in motion.&amp;nbsp; Sometimes, I sleep in the back, sometimes, I play games on my phone, but more often than not, I would be bored.&amp;nbsp; Fortunately, once a while, we stop on the side of the road to take pictures, and Steve would entertain us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;padding-top: 0px;padding-left: 0px;padding-right: 0px;border: 0px&quot; title=&quot;sign1&quot; alt=&quot;sign1&quot; src=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;lastresponders.org&amp;#47;wp-content&amp;#47;uploads&amp;#47;2014&amp;#47;04&amp;#47;sign1.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1028&quot; height=&quot;675&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; &amp;#47;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;padding-top: 0px;padding-left: 0px;padding-right: 0px;border: 0px&quot; title=&quot;sign2&quot; alt=&quot;sign2&quot; src=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;lastresponders.org&amp;#47;wp-content&amp;#47;uploads&amp;#47;2014&amp;#47;04&amp;#47;sign2.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1028&quot; height=&quot;667&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; &amp;#47;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;padding-top: 0px;padding-left: 0px;padding-right: 0px;border: 0px&quot; title=&quot;sign3_edited&quot; alt=&quot;sign3_edited&quot; src=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;lastresponders.org&amp;#47;wp-content&amp;#47;uploads&amp;#47;2014&amp;#47;04&amp;#47;sign3_edited.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1028&quot; height=&quot;671&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; &amp;#47;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2014 00:11:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2014/04/21/in-boredom.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2014/04/21/in-boredom.html</guid>
        
        <category>Last Responders</category>
        
        <category>lastresponders</category>
        
        
        <category>Cathy</category>
        
        <category>South America Rally 2013</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Last of Team Last Responders in the Deserts of Peru</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #0000ff&quot;&gt;T&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: medium&quot;&gt;hree out of seven members of Team Last Responders remained together after Trujillo, Peru.&amp;nbsp; Ken left months ago in Mexico City; in Trujillo, Stephen Alexis went on his speed travel to Patagonia, Mike and Paul retuned home, with no answers on how &lt;a href=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;www.viveperu.org&amp;#47;&quot;&gt;Vive Peru&lt;&amp;#47;a&gt; would receive the donation of the vehicles, Martha, Steve, and Cathy continued to travel to Bolivia.&amp;nbsp; We plan to visit &lt;a href=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;www.esperanca.org&amp;#47;&quot;&gt;Esperanca&lt;&amp;#47;a&gt; in Bolivia while &lt;a href=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;www.viveperu.org&amp;#47;&quot;&gt;Vive Peru&lt;&amp;#47;a&gt; sorts out the donation process. As the team headed out of Trujillo, Martha wanted to put the extra Jeep keys on her keychain, forgetting that we left the Jeep behind; when entering a crowded city, Cathy looked into the side mirror of the ambulance to see whether the Jeep was following, also forgetting the Jeep was no longer there; Steve, well, Steve has been focusing on an iPhone game and has not yet had the leisure to express his emotions.&lt;&amp;#47;span&gt;&lt;&amp;#47;span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #ff0000;font-family: Comic Sans MS;font-size: large&quot;&gt;Woman and Her Camera&lt;&amp;#47;span&gt;&lt;&amp;#47;strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;padding-top: 0px;padding-left: 0px;padding-right: 0px;border-width: 0px&quot; title=&quot;woman_camera&quot; alt=&quot;woman_camera&quot; src=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;lastresponders.org&amp;#47;wp-content&amp;#47;uploads&amp;#47;2014&amp;#47;04&amp;#47;woman_camera.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1028&quot; height=&quot;613&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; &amp;#47;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #0000ff;font-family: Comic Sans MS;font-size: medium&quot;&gt;Description &amp;ndash; This woman works diligently around the clock to produce content for the team.&amp;nbsp; She spends hours everyday taking pictures, selecting pictures, and editing videos.&amp;nbsp; Since Mike&amp;rsquo;s departure, this poor woman&amp;rsquo;s work increased tremendously, she had to climb up a tower to take photos with 2 film cameras and 3 digital cameras while her teammates sat around and poked each other in boredom.&amp;nbsp; Without her, the South America journey would be unimaginable if not impossible.&lt;&amp;#47;span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #ff0000;font-family: Comic Sans MS;font-size: large&quot;&gt;Man and His Ambulance&lt;&amp;#47;span&gt;&lt;&amp;#47;strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;padding-top: 0px;padding-left: 0px;padding-right: 0px;border-width: 0px&quot; title=&quot;man_ambulance_edited&quot; alt=&quot;man_ambulance_edited&quot; src=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;lastresponders.org&amp;#47;wp-content&amp;#47;uploads&amp;#47;2014&amp;#47;04&amp;#47;man_ambulance_edited.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1028&quot; height=&quot;643&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; &amp;#47;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #0000ff;font-family: Comic Sans MS;font-size: medium&quot;&gt;Description &amp;ndash; This man is known to go on rallies delivering ambulances to charities around the world.&amp;nbsp; He enjoys challenges and loves to tell rally stories.&amp;nbsp; His daily tasks are: setting goals for the team, driving, writing emails and blog posts, and tolerating Cathy&amp;rsquo;s endless nagging. While most of his teammates regard him as a good leader, it should also be known that on the rally, he rarely showers, never washes his clothes, and &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: line-through&quot;&gt;h&lt;&amp;#47;span&gt;as very stinky feet.&lt;&amp;#47;span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #ff0000;font-family: Comic Sans MS;font-size: large&quot;&gt;Witch Calling to the Sea&lt;&amp;#47;span&gt;&lt;&amp;#47;strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;padding-top: 0px;padding-left: 0px;padding-right: 0px;border-width: 0px&quot; title=&quot;witch_sea&quot; alt=&quot;witch_sea&quot; src=&quot;http:&amp;#47;&amp;#47;lastresponders.org&amp;#47;wp-content&amp;#47;uploads&amp;#47;2014&amp;#47;04&amp;#47;witch_sea.jpg&quot; width=&quot;1028&quot; height=&quot;717&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; &amp;#47;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #0000ff;font-family: Comic Sans MS;font-size: medium&quot;&gt;Description &amp;ndash; [in all fairness] Intentionally Left Blank &lt;&amp;#47;span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2014 21:15:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://lastresponders.org/2014/04/13/the-last-of-team-last-responders-in-the-deserts-of-peru.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://lastresponders.org/2014/04/13/the-last-of-team-last-responders-in-the-deserts-of-peru.html</guid>
        
        <category>Travel</category>
        
        <category>Last Responders</category>
        
        <category>lastresponders</category>
        
        <category>Peru</category>
        
        <category>desert</category>
        
        
        <category>Cathy</category>
        
        <category>South America Rally 2013</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
